{
    "subject": "resource/Ron_Fenton",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/South_Shields",
    "human_readable": "Ron Fenton was born in South Shields.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9170188903808594,
            "question": "Is Ron Fenton from South Shields?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7927091717720032,
            "question": "Where was Ron Fenton born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.775784969329834,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Ron Fenton and South Shields?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47268861532211304,
            "question": "Do you know anything else about people born in South Shields?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3307376503944397,
            "question": "What are some famous people from South Shields?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3106284737586975,
            "question": "What is Ron Fenton known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30736681818962097,
            "question": "Where might Ron Fenton have lived?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2156076729297638,
            "question": "Do you have information about other people named Ron Fenton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1544085294008255,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Ron Fenton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05617441609501839,
            "question": "What is the significance of birth place?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ron Fenton was born in South Shields.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3346_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Ron Fenton?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3346_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you have information about other people named Ron Fenton?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3346_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might Ron Fenton have lived?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3346_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3346_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3346_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3346_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3346_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3346_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3346_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3346_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3346_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3346_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3346_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the documents, I found that:\n\n* The document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3346/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt mentions that \"Ron Fenton was born in South Shields\".\n* This information is also confirmed by other documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3346/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3346/re-ranker-msmarco/34.txt) which state that \"Fenton was born in South Shields\".\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Ronald Fenton (Ron Fenton) was born in South Shields, which directly supports the statement that Ron Fenton was born in South Shields."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}